Welcome to this short course,
Automated Testing for LLM Ops,
built in partnership with CircleCI.
Software testing helps
you identify bugs
and security vulnerabilities
in your applications,
and automated testing frees up your
time and energy further, so they can
focus on the creative parts of
designing and building
your application. In this course,
you learn modern
software engineering practices
focused on testing
for the practical
development and deployment of LLM-based
applications.
Two kinds of LLM
evaluations that you implement
in this course are rule-based
evaluations and model-graded evaluations.
Rule-based evals use string
or pattern matching, for
example, regular
expression matching, and
are fast and cost-effective to
run.
I use these whenever I
want to evaluate outputs that
have a clear right answer,
such as sentiment
classification and if, say,
you have ground-truth labels.
Rule-based
evals are quick and cheap to run, so
you can run these
tests every time you
commit a code change
to get fast feedback
on the health of
your application.
Model graded evaluations
are relevant for
applications where there
are many possible good or bad
outputs.
For example, if you ask an LLM
to write text content for you,
there can be more than one high-quality
response.
Here, you might prompt
an evaluation LLM to have it
assess the quality of the output
of your application LLM.
In other words,
use an LLM to evaluate
the output of another LLM.
Model-graded evals take more time
and cost more, but
they allow you to
assess more complex outputs.
I'm delighted to introduce our
instructor for this course, Rob
Zuber, Chief
Technology Officer for CircleCI.
Rob has spent
decades leading engineering
teams and also
helping customers scale
up their software
delivery practice by
making processes repeatable,
scalable, and reliable.
He'll show you how to do this for your
applications as well with
an emphasis on testing.
Thanks, Andrew.
In your software development process,
you and your teammates may commit
code updates or bug fixes multiple
times per day.
In this course, you'll learn to set
triggers that automatically
run your evaluations
whenever you or
your teammates commit
code changes to
the repository.
Your team may also
release updated versions of
the app on a broader cadence,
perhaps once every two weeks.
Before deploying to users,
you can also automate more holistic,
comprehensive, pre-release
evaluations.
For per-commit evals, you
can include rules-based evaluations
because they're fast and
cheap to run.
And for those pre-release evals, you
can include rules-based evaluations
because they're fast and
cheap to run. And for those
pre-release evals, it may be very
helpful to use model-graded evals to do more
thorough testing before deployment.
By the end of the course,
you will combine per-commit and pre-release evals
into an automated
testing suite.
And for this course, you'll
design tests to detect
hallucinations in LLM responses.
Many people have worked
to make this course possible. I'd
like to thank on the CircleCI side, Michael
Webster, Jacob Schmidt, and
Emma Webb.
From DeepLearning.ai, Eddie Hsu and Eshmal
Gargari have also
contributed to this course.
The first lesson will
be a quick overview
of continuous integration terms
and technologies that we'll
use as the foundation
for building our automated
LLM testing pipeline.
When you finish this course,
that will be a
real testament to your
dedication to building good
applications.
Or if you're not sure how much you'll use
these ideas, you can
still test the waters.
So let's go on to the next
video to get started.